▍2026 辛辛那提 WTA1000 1/8决赛
凯斯 7-6(3) 6-4 王曦雨 · 赛后场上采访
Madison Keys makes it
凯斯
through to the quarterfinals once again
再次杀进这里的1/4决赛
in Cincinnati.
辛辛那提
The former champion finding her way past
这位辛辛那提前冠军淘汰了
the Chinese qualifier Wong Xiu 7664.
中国资格赛选手王曦雨 7-6 6-4
She certainly had to work for it though.
她确实费了不少力气
But work she did and found a route
但她找到了办法
through in straight sets.
直落两盘拿下
She'll be very pleased with that I
她应该会很满意
would imagine.
我猜
now awaits either Selk or Arena Sabalena
下轮对手是萨卡里或萨巴伦卡
in the quarterfinals.
二者之一
Maddie, congratulations.
麦迪 恭喜你
You You were incredible.
你太厉害了
I mean,
我是说
obviously this place brought the love,
这里的球迷给了你很多爱
but you brought the fight.
但你带来了斗志
I mean, to see you fight
看你最后那段
at the end was incredible.
拼得太不可思议了
What were you most happy with tonight?
今晚你最满意哪一点？
I mean, obviously getting down
一开始
to break early in that first set,
第一盘早早被破发
just trying to get that back as quickly
就想着尽快追回来
as possible.
越快越好
And I mean, she played great.
而且她打得真的很好
So, really just trying to hang
所以我就想着守住
on and keep the lead and then as soon
保持领先
as I lost it, just trying to get it back
一旦丢了就赶紧追回来
as quickly as possible.
越快越好
And obviously it's so easy to play here
在这里打球特别轻松
when you have amazing fans
有这么棒的球迷
and you have the crowd cheering for you
全场都在为你加油
and getting you
帮你
through the tough moments.
撑过那些艰难时刻
It is your first WTA 1000 quarterfinal
这是你本赛季第一次
of the season.
打进WTA1000的1/4决赛
You have done so much in the sport.
你在这项运动里已经拿到很多
What matters to you most at this stage?
到了这个阶段 你最看重什么？
Is it the joy?
是快乐吗？
Is it a certain number of wins?
还是胜场数？
Is it a certain caliber of trophies?
还是奖杯的分量？
What motivates you most?
什么最能激励你？
I think the biggest thing
我觉得最重要的一点
is that I'm still out here and I'm still playing
是我还在这里 还在打
some really good tennis.
而且打得真的不错
I started quite a long time ago
我出道已经很久了
at this point, but being able
但还能够
to come back and still be competitive
回来之后依然有竞争力
and it's really just putting myself
就是不断把自己
in these positions to go deep
放到这样的位置上打得更深
in these big events
在这些大赛里
and just kind of remind everyone
也算是提醒大家
that everyone calls me a veteran,
都叫我老将
but I can still play some good tennis.
但我照样能打好球
And just kind of reminding myself
也是提醒我自己
of that.
这一点
After a win like this, like what
赢了这样一场之后
does a night look like for you?
你今晚会怎么过？
Is it you relax?
放松一下吗？
You're going to watch a show?
看部剧？
Are you going to get
会去
in the comments regarding the podcast,
看播客底下的评论吗
a burger with everything on it?
还是吃个加满料的汉堡？
Like, what does celebration look like
你的庆祝方式
for you?
是什么样的？
You know, I think it's wrapping up
大概就是收个尾
the kind of business end of the day
把该做的事做完
with some recovery and then I like to I'm
做点恢复训练 然后
the queen of being asleep by 10 o'clock,
我可是十点就睡觉的女王
so we have a little bit of time to go.
所以还有点时间
So, I'm going to be on a tight schedule
我得抓紧时间
to try to get in bed by my bedtime.
争取按时上床
But just kind of wind down
就是放松下来
and enjoy the win.
享受这场胜利
Try to fall asleep and hopefully get a full 8
争取睡个八
to 9 hours of sleep.
九个小时
Wow. We could all learn from this level
哇 这份自律
of discipline.
我们都该学学
Show some love for everyone.
把掌声送给
Quarterfinalist Madison Keys.
1/4决赛选手 凯斯